(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-11T00:52:02.063078",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Hello, welcome to my 3D live.
My 3D live, I've actually— happy 2 years!
I kind of want to go somewhere really nice.
Look at the sky, look at how beautiful the weather is.
I wouldn't call this weather... Look at this beautiful weather!
I wanna— I wanna go somewhere nice. Where should I go?
Oh, wait.
Ah, oh!
It's a heli!
It's a heli! We have a helicopter!
Wait, wait, I wanna—
I wanna— I wanna ride a heli!
This is like my 3D showcase, actually.
I remember that I wrote a heli once.
What do we do? What do we do?
Woah!
We're actually flying!
Wait, what? We're actually flying!
Oh my god, we're flying! We're flying!
Eh, sugoi!
Whoa, amazing!
We're flying, chat!
Woah!
Let me get out of here.
I can't get out of here. Wait, now I can.
Oh! Woah, bye-bye!
Bye, heli!
Woah, that was so cool!
And that's a grand entrance, isn't it?
Befitting for me, the best agent in the world!
Huh?
What are you looking at?
You're late to your missions, Secretary!
I know you're so— You were supposed to be waiting for me at the stage, and now, to do your mission...
I know you were supposed to be waiting for me at the stage, and now, to do your mission...
and to greet me once I get off the helicopter, but now what are you doing?
You're doing nothing but waving a lightstick!
Is this what you were born to do?
I'm so aggressive.
Wait, watch this, watch this, okay? Watch this.
Woah, guests are here!
Zetacharies, oh.
No, hello.
Why don't you guys say something?
Hello?
You guys are lifeless.
Sometimes I feel lifeless too.
Okay, what about— What about this chat?
Watch this.
Isn't the stage beautiful?
I was going to show you off the stage earlier, but I forgot.
Um, I have two-second memory.
Um, I have a two-second memory.
So, look at the beautiful skies!
I wanted something like, um, really magical, something like starry night, lang-it...
You know? Lang-it... like anything related to gastronomy, wait!
You know? Lang-it... like anything related to gastronomy— Wait!
Astronomy!
Not gastronomy, that's stomach, holy crap!
Um, astronomy! Look, there's a shooting star!
There's a shooting star! Make a wish.
Make a wish.
What did you make a wish?
What did you make a wish for?
You guys have to make a wish.
Oh, what do you think about this one?
Do you know what it says there?
It says Zeta on the stage, because you guys will be...
Wait, Zeta is— Zeta is the best thing that could have...
What's wrong with my speech? That could ever happen...
What could ever happen in your life?
Um... yoyo-yoyo. Oh, wait, look at this one.
Are you guys ready? Sorry, I was like trying to talk while I maneuver through this thing.
I'm very new to VR, so...
this is very, very difficult for me.
I am entering a whole new world, you know?
But yeah, I was thinking since it's our two years anniversary on this channel, I was thinking why not celebrate...
But yeah, I was thinking since it's our two-year anniversary on this channel, I was thinking why not celebrate...
um, me being two years old?
I'm so young.
Me being, uh... I want to say, if I've been streaming for two years, does that mean I'm old now?
Like, is two years old old? Like, hello?
Um, yoyo-yoyo.
What about um...
Watch this.
Oh,
hello, I'm back, chat.
I know you missed my 2D face.
And it's like, you guys are probably like, "Where's Zeta? I don't want to see the stage."
How dare you?
Huh?
This stage was made with lots of love and care.
How dare you not want to see the stage?
Anyways,
um, I'll show you around.
Uh, as you guys can see, you are in the back waving, um, waving that light stick with no single thought in your head, just like me.
If you want to get closer, you might notice that I have no single thought.
Oh, I look like I have a mohawk here.
Jijik banget. Jijik banget kalau kayak gini.
And yeah, ooh!
Okay, I'm not used to holding a selfie stick, so if, oh, well,
if it gets turned around, then I'm sorry.
Well, I have a bunch of things that I wanted to show you. Watch this, okay?
Wait! Whoa!
Heh!
You probably didn't know what just happened.
Ah, I'm tired. I want to lay down.
I want to lay down.
Break time's over.
Okay.
Watch this, I have...
Whoa, bom, bom, bom, bom!
Watch this! Chibi, chibi, chibi, chibi...
I've always wanted to rap in this, like, stage made just for me, you know? I thought it would be cool. I'm just like, "Yeah."
Yo, yo, yo, mic check one, two, the next rapper in town. What, what was my rapper name again?
Um, DJ DJV V DJV7 or something? I don't remember, to be honest.
Damn, I have, like, two-second memory, like a goldfish.
Oh, wait, oh, with a mic, too. I should have done it with a mic.
Yo, yo, yo, yo, yo!
Wah!
Watch, watch me hit you with this mic! Bam! Wha! Wha!
Oh, um, this might be a little bit more tame. I won't I won't hit you anymore, okay? I won't hit you anymore. Ready for the surprise?
Ready for the surprise?
I won't hit you anymore.
Funny evil thoughts.
It's a cat. What do you think?
How does the cat go? Dance go again.
Yeah, it's a cat.
Do you like it? I'm going to do a 360 for you. 360 no scope, baby.
Woo, spin!
Wait, I can actually do spinning in real time now. Wait. Woo!
Wait, I can... Oh, I'm so dizzy.
I'm so motion-sick.
Thank you very much. I'm so motion-sick.
Why did you do that to me? Why did you make me motion-sick?
You know that I'm prone to motion sickness. Why did you do?
This is probably the most motion-sick-inducing VR concert, not... Okay, I should stop calling it a concert. It's not a concert.
It's more like a fun free talk, zatsuu, you know, zatsuu.
Like fun segment. So free talk?
I would consider it free talk. We're doing a lot of free talk here and a lot of, um, camera smashing, um, motion-sick-inducing stuff.
Uh, would you like to keep me Would you like for me to keep the cat ears on or not?
Because I feel like you guys would appreciate my hair more since my hair already looks like the ears anyway, so I don't think we need it. We don't need it. Look, pretty much the same.
Okay, oh no! I just I literally just admitted it. No, it's not the same. That's hair, okay?
Shut up, furries. It's this is hair. You can't just equate anything remotely hair-like to animals.
Um, I have a guess. I have a guess on this special anniversary stream, and that is...
Bazz...
Bazz'so!
What are you thinking?
Is it cute?
Very cute, right?
Wah wah wah
So cute.
Wait, if I bend over, maybe you guys will be able to see better.
This is Bazz'so.
Isn't it so cute?
Wait, come closer.
That's not me.
What the?
This one, this way.
What you doing, baby girl?
Yeah, this is Bazz'so, very cute. I know you guys love Bazz'so more than me sometimes.
Mmm... What else, what else?
Oh, I have my usual emotes, if you remember, type this in chat.
My usual emote, wait, watch this...
It's the Strip W strip, my usual emote.
Um, I have a really sad, sad mode as well. Watch this...
Watch this, okay?
Be prepared to be sad, everyone!
Be prepared to to be prepared to sad.
What is wrong with my English today?
Yep, yep, nangis. Lihat ini, okay?
Yep, yep, crying. Look at this, okay?
It's such a tragic day today, Zeta turned two years old!
Wait, watch this, I can go even sadder.
Please! No! Don't take my...
Don't take my uh... what is it called? Don't take my expired food away! No!
Don't take my coffee away!
What about this? Mmm... What do you guys think about this one?
You eat veggies? You are so disgusting! Just kidding.
And this one. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
The thing is, with um with this uh chibi body, I can't really like my movement is very limited, but you know, I can still move around and have fun with you guys, so I don't think that's too much of a problem, you know.
This is a happy happy one, but watch this.
何そんなことできるの？何そんなことできないの？
How can you even do that? Why can't you even do that?
Ha? Why can't you even do that? That's just such a simple thing. Why can't you just wash the dishes?
Huh? Why can't you even do that? That's just such a simple thing. Why can't you just wash the dishes?
This is smug. This is smug. Gakkijeta! Sorry, I keep hitting the mic, you're probably gonna die. Um, yeah, this is Gakkijeta, you know?
Wait, give me one second.
Watch this. Kira kira! Kira kira!
You guys already seen this one, but me, when I don't get my daily intake of coffee... Where's my coffee?
You guys have already seen this one, but me, when I don't get my daily intake of coffee... Where's my coffee?
Okay, well, I am excited to show you guys um what we have in store today. I was thinking we can do a little bit of free talk and maybe um some songs in between, you know?
You know, what do you guys think? Uh, I kind of want to like um I don't know, I I I have no thoughts. I I the thing is I don't I just the thing is I just don't think...
I'm just gonna chill with you guys today and do whatever feels best. If I if I wanted to do a backflip, then I...
What about this?
This is cute.
This one is cute.
Cute!
Ha!
You.
This one's cute.
Okay! Well,
I will show you.
Let's get back into position. Okay, okay.
Let's get back into position.
And I want you guys to have fun with me, okay?
This is nothing serious, so please,
let's all just like have fun together, you know?
Have fun together, enjoy these moments together, and...
Yeah, if you guys know the song, you can sing along, but if you don't, then that's fine too.
Just... if you don't...
If you don't, you can just sit there and wave the...
You can just sit there and wave the stick, okay?
あなたのアイドル サインはB
Your idol, sign is B!
サインはBッ！
Sign is B!
ピーこま、すぐフォア！
P-Komai, right to the fore!
予約だって嬉しいね 街頭敷いて足音バタバタしながら
Making reservations is so exciting, spreading the red carpet, pattering my feet,
今日楽しみで切れなかったよ
I couldn't sleep because I was so excited for today!
人生の中身あるかないかじゃない
It's not about whether life has substance;
1分1秒無駄になんてできないさ 始めましょう
we can't waste a single minute or second. Let's get started!
君も君も君も お出迎えさま
You, you, and you too, welcome!
手を鳴らせ いらっしゃいませ 好きが集まる場所へようこそ
Clap your hands, welcome, welcome to the place where passions gather!
日常は黒くの中 ここに来たなら踊りゃんしゃん ちょっとイガイが今いいか関係ない
Everyday life is in black, but if you came here, dance away! It doesn't matter if you have a slight irritation right now.
瞳大き小さいとか気にしない ちゃんと見えてる君のサイリウム
Don't worry about whether your eyes are big or small. I can clearly see your penlight!
今僕らコケバ飛ぶような 小さな小さな才能だけど 私を
Right now, we're like a little talent that flies when it trips, but...
推してくれないもんな 枠レスを上げる
you won't support us? Let's raise the framerate!
あなたのアイドル サインはBッ！
Your idol, sign is B!
エスわありがとだってだって 誓い将来自慢して欲しいよ
"S" stands for thank you, because I want you to brag about this oath in the future!
こうしてられない 君と君と今を楽しまなきゃ
We can't stay like this; we've to enjoy the present with you and you!
聞き込みも瞳見知りも 目だんだん違う顔見せてよ
Even if you're shy or a stranger, show me a different face little by little.
みんなちょうだい 調子どうだい 何振り返るまずに そうそうそう
Everyone give it to me, how are you doing? Without looking back, yes, yes, yes!
光笑われなくても関係ない 真剣月夜過ぎ
It doesn't matter if people laugh at the light, the night is too serious.
君もサイリウム さて世界が私を拒んで
You too, your penlight! Now, even if the world rejects me,
ひとりぼっちを感じたとしても あなたが味方でいてくれたら 怖いものはないよ
even if I feel all alone, as long as you're on my side, there's nothing to be afraid of!
ピーこま、すぐフォア！
P-Komai, right to the fore!
見せてよ見せてよ 何か始まる 君との物語が ああなんて素晴らしい景色だ
Show me, show me, something is starting, our story together—ah, what a wonderful scenery!
人がようが今いいか関係ない 剥が大き小さいとか気にしない
It doesn't matter what people say right now. Don't worry about whether it's big or small.
ちゃんと見えてる君のサイリウム
I can clearly see your penlight!
今僕らコケバ飛ぶような 小さな小さな才能だけど私を
Right now, we're like a little talent that flies when it trips, but...
押してくれないもんな 枠レスを上げる
you won't support us? Let's raise the framerate!
あなたのアイドル サインはBッ！
Your idol, sign is B!
Yay! How was it?
Did you wave your light sticks around?
Did you?
I saw you in the audience that you weren't waving your light sticks, you were just staying still.
Um, so next song,
so next song is something, something you guys might really like.
is something you guys might really like.
What do you think it is?
I wanted something really like groovy,
I wanted something really groovy...
really like slow,
really slow,
cuz lately I've been really into like, like sweet, but like slow songs, you know?
'cause lately I've been really into sweet, slow songs, you know?
What if I bring a friend with me?
What do you guys think? Should I bring Should I bring a friend with me?
What do you guys think? Should I bring a friend with me?
Can you can you see?
Can you see?
I'm going to bring him along as well.
バズのこと好き？バズ好き？バズ好き？
Do you like Bazu? Do you? Do you?
好きはダメだよ。You can't like Bazu.
You can't like him. You can't like Bazu.
Bazu's mine. He's my spouse forever. You can't like him.
Well, and on that note, I have a song related to a person or someone that you can't like, okay?
Well, on that note, I have a song about someone you're not allowed to like, okay?
So let's go!
Next song!
好きになっちゃダメな人
Suki ni Naccha Dame na Hito
好きになっちゃほろ負けじゃん
I'm the loser for falling for you,
勝てるわけないじゃん
there's no way I can win.
最初から分かってた
I knew that from the start.
あなたは あなたは 好きになっちゃダメな人
You are... someone I shouldn't love.
あなたの好きってどんな好き？
What kind of "like" do you feel?
多分わたしとは違う好き
Probably different from mine.
可愛いなんて言葉でごまかさないで
Don't brush it off with words like "cute."
大事にされてることは痛いほど分かるけれど
I know all too well how much you cherish me,
何かが足りない 違うそうじゃない気持ちが知りたい
but something's missing. I want to know how you really feel.
わたし大きくなったよ
I've grown up, you know?
背伸びしたら届きそうな あなたの唇
If I stretch, I can almost reach your lips.
子供扱いしないでよ
Don't treat me like a child!
ほらまた頭をくしゃって くしゃってする
See, you're messing up my hair again...
好きになっちゃほろ負けじゃん 勝てるわけないじゃん
I'm the loser for falling, I can't win against you.
そのずるい笑顔に飲み込まれてく
I get swallowed up by that sly smile of yours.
好きになっちゃほろ負けじゃん こんなのってないじゃん
I'm the loser for falling, this isn't fair at all.
最初から分かってた あなたは あなたは
I knew that from the start. You are, you are...
好きになっちゃダメな人
someone I shouldn't fall in love with.
想いに気づくタイミングは たくさんあったはずなのに
There should've been so many times to realize my feelings,
私かわいらしくない ホント素直じゃない
but I'm not cute, and I'm not being honest.
このまま消えたい
I just want to disappear like this.
気持ちが膨ら上がるたび
Every time my feelings swell up,
バレるのが悔しくて 隠した横顔
I hate getting caught and hide my profile away.
世界でたった一人の 存在だと知ってしまって 涙が出る
Knowing you're the only one in the world makes me cry.
好きにならない方が無理じゃん 叶うわけないじゃん
It's impossible not to fall, there's no way this comes true.
ずっと心のなか 住みついている
You've been living deep inside my heart all this time.
好きにならない方が無理じゃん どうしようもないじゃん
It's impossible not to fall, there's nothing I can do.
最初から決まってた あなたは あなたは
It was decided from the start. You are, you are...
多分きっと運命の人
probably, surely, my destined person.
「特別」と思うとやっぱり あなたの一挙一挙一動が気になって気になって
When I think you're special, every little move you make gets to me.
好きになっちゃほろ負けじゃん 勝てるわけないじゃん
I'm the loser for falling for you, there's no way I can win.
そのずるい笑顔に飲み込まれてく
I get swallowed up by that sly smile of yours.
好きになっちゃほろ負けじゃん こんなのってないじゃん
I'm the loser for falling for you, this isn't fair at all.
最初から分かってた あなたは あなたは
I knew that from the start. You are, you are...
好きになっちゃダメな人
someone I shouldn't fall in love with.
See, I told you it was groovy, right?
Now, I'm ready to sing the next song.
So, are you ready? Are you ready? Are you ready?
Oh, I want to sing, um...
Gimana sih? Mau nyanyi, kameramen ya?
How is it? You want to sing, cameraman?
Gimana sih? Mutar-mutar enggak jelas. Hey!
How is it? Spinning around vaguely. Hey!
Di sini, di sini. Gini, di sini. Di sini, di sini, bukan di sana.
Here, here. Like this, here. Here, here, not there.
Sudahlah, whatever. Uh.
Whatever. Uh.
Okay, so next song, I'm gonna be singing...
Okay, so for the next song, I'm gonna be singing...
Are you guys still staying with me? Don't get motion sick, okay?
Are you staying with me? You're gonna stay with me for the next song, right?
Okay, let's go.
What if I just sit down? What if I just sit down?
Oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah.
Okay, never mind. It hurts. Ah ya ya ya.
Enggak usah, enggak usah.
No need, no need.
Gimana sih? Segini aja deh.
How is it? Let's just do it like this.
Okay, ready?
To you... Yes, my love, to you...
Yes, my love, to you... You... To you...
私わ 私 あなたわ あなたと
I am myself, and you are you...
憶えていた そんな気もするわ
I feel like I said that last night...
グレーのジャケットに 見覚えがある コーヒーのしみ
The coffee stain on the gray jacket looks familiar...
相変わらずなのね ショウウインドウに二人写れば
You're still the same, aren't you? If we see ourselves in the shop window...
Stay with me 真夜中のドアをたたき
Stay with me, knocking on the midnight door...
帰らないでと泣いた あの季節が今目の前
I cried, don't go back, that season is right in front of my eyes now...
Stay with me 口ぐせを言いながら 二人の時間を抱いて
Stay with me, while saying my favorite words, holding onto our time together...
まだ忘れず大事にしていた
Still not forgetting, treasuring it...
恋と愛とは 違うものだよと
Love and romance are different things...
二度目の冬が来て 離れていったあなたの心
Winter comes for the second time, your heart that was distant from me...
振り返ればいつも そこにあなたを感じていたの
Looking back, I always felt you there...
Stay with me 真夜中のドアをたたき
Stay with me, knocking on the midnight door...
心に穴があいた あの季節が今目の前
A hole opened in my heart, that season is right in front of me now...
Stay with me 淋しさ紛らわして 置いたレコードの針
Stay with me, warding off loneliness, the needle on the record...
同じメロディ 繰り返していた
Repeating the same melody...
Stay with me 真夜中のドアをたたき
Stay with me, knocking on the midnight door...
帰らないでと泣いた あの季節が今目の前
I cried, don't go back, that season is right in front of me now...
Stay with me
ぐちぐち言いながら
While grumbling and complaining,
ふたりの時を抱いて
embracing our time together.
まだ忘れず 温めてた
Still not forgetting, keeping it warm.
Stay with me
真夜中のドアをたたき
knocking on the midnight door,
帰らないでと泣いた
crying, "Don't go back."
あの季節が 今目の前
That season is right before my eyes now.
Stay with me
ぐちぐち言いながら
while grumbling and complaining,
ふたりの時を抱いて
embracing our time together.
まだ忘れず 温めてた
Still not forgetting, keeping it warm.
Stay with me
真夜中のドアをたたき
knocking on the midnight door,
帰らないでと泣いた
crying, "Don't go back."
あの季節が 今目の前
That season is right before my eyes now.
Did you stay during those concerts?
Did you leave?
I saw two or three people just left.
Even though the song was called "Stay With Me",
why did people still leave?
Heartless. Human beings are so heartless.
かっこいいあたし！
Cool me!
You know, this song, "Stay With Me",
I've been singing it in unarchived karaoke...
I sang a lot of versions of "Stay With Me".
So this was my... chibi version.
I hope you guys liked that one because the next one is even more...
Don't be scared, the next one is even more sickeningly sweet!
But I have a surprise because the next one, just like the previous song...
Oh, I forgot to mention this because I'm dumb, but the previous song I sang was with...
This song as well, I'm gonna have Fubuki come take over my body and sing for me.
Is that okay? So we're gonna welcome Fubuki here, okay?
Fubuki! Where are you?
Fubuki!
五線譜に書き出す
Writing it out on the staff lines,
感情任せの想いを綴って
spelling out emotions driven by feelings.
繰り返し消してみては
Repeatedly erasing and trying again,
ありふれたセリフばかり
it's just full of clichéd lines.
「あなた以外は要らない」なんて
Saying "I don't need anyone other than you,"
簡単な恋や愛だけじゃ まだ
simple love and romance alone aren't enough yet.
語り切れないよ
I can't fully express it.
愛しいだけじゃ足りないよ
Affection alone isn't enough,
歌に乗せて送りたい
I want to put it in a song and send it.
息継ぎすら忘れるほど あなたを紡ぐ
Spinning you to the point of forgetting to breathe.
止まらない物足りなさは 頭じゃ分かってても
Even though my head understands the unending dissatisfaction,
でもまだ声には出せないの
I still can't voice it out.
幼小説の中
Inside a juvenile novel,
不細工な心まとめられたらな
if I could gather up my clumsy heart...
打ち明け好きないよ 二度と下手なふりして踊けた
Playing clumsy and fooling around once more.
私思うと 見ていて欲しい なんて今夜
When I think of myself, I want you to watch.
限りないメロディを 消えてくれたりしないから
A melody without end, because it won't fade.
数えきれないフレーズも 二度と出せない響きも
Countless phrases, and resonances anew,
伝えたいよ 奇生点血はいらないから
I want to convey them to you.
何も手につかないほど 奏でていることが
Playing to the point of losing touch,
今ね また窓を開け物作ってくわルーム
Now I open the window to craft a room...
ただひたすらあなた歌うよ
I will simply sing for you.
声をからして叫んだよ
I cried out until my voice was hoarse.
腹が立つくらいの愛 吐き出しても体温だけ上がったままで
Even with love that makes my temperature rise,
奥は求めたりしない あなたを愛するためだけに 生まれたなのに自信ないままの歌声
Born only to love you without any doubts,
いつか綺麗に透き通る 愛してるを
Someday, a clear and pure "I love you"—
愛してるを
"I love you."
Woo! Hey hey hey hey hey!
How is that? Are you guys happy?
So we're on to the next song, which will make you guys even more happy! Are you guys happy?
So we're on to the next song!
I haven't heard your voice. Hello? Are you happy?
I haven't heard your voice. Hello?
Senang ya? Senang ya?
Happy, huh? Happy, huh?
It's so weird talking to myself in VR.
It's okay, I'm used to it. Are you guys happy because I'm the happiest?
Are you guys happy because I'm happiest?
You know, you know what makes me so happy? Now that I think about it, I have one thing that makes me so happy.
You know what makes me so happy? One thing.
Bam! Cats! Cats!
I'm thinking for so- for my next song, it's something related to happiness, I think. Sometimes, you know, when you get too happy, you start to question yourself, you're like...
Next song is about happiness. Sometimes you question it...
Hmm, is it really okay for me to be this happy?
Hmm, is it really okay to be this happy?
Senang ya, boros ya? Boros seneng ya? Ha? Senang ya? Senang ya?
Happy, right? Splurging on happiness?
So, I think this next song I'm going to be wearing this... something that makes me happy.
For this next song, I'll wear something happy.
Don't... I know what you guys are about to say. You guys are going to say that I have six ears, which is just not true. It's three all! I don't have six ears!
I don't have six ears! It's three!
Okay, let me get ready. Should I go on all fours like a furry? First... is this?
Should I go on all fours like a furry? Like this?
Kucing, kucing, kucing jalan-jalan di sini.
Cat, cat, cat walking around here.
Bukannya orang nggak sih? Kalau misalnya mulai lagunya dari belakang apa dari sini ya?
Should I start the song from the back?
Udah deh. Nggak split, guys, si jangan-jangan. Ya udah, gini aja. Berdiri aja deh.
Never mind. Let's just stand up.
Get ready... Okay, I'm ready.
超めでたいソング 〜こんなに幸せでいいのかな？〜
Cho Medetai Song
超めでたい！超めでたい！超めでたい！超めでたい！
Super congratulations!
本日晴れの日 雨でも晴れ
Today's a clear day, even in the rain it's sunny!
一生に一度のトエブリデイ
Once-in-a-lifetime everyday,
だけどやっぱり今天是スペシャル
but today is definitely special!
本日の衣装は悩みません
I didn't worry about today's outfit at all!
一周回ってマシンプるだけど
It's all the way around and simple, but
あれでもやっぱ派手すぎ？
is it still too flashy?
来年の今は記念日
Next year's today is an anniversary,
それまではたくさんもっと
and until then, more and more—
どうでもいいことと貯金とかもしょ
saving up random stuff and money!
そして大事なこと
And most importantly,
まずはトゥデイをブチ上げよう
let's pump up today right now!
私こんなに幸せでいいのかな？
I wonder if it's okay to be this happy?
なんて本当はそのこと悩んでないけど
Though I'm not really worrying about that,
だってちょっとくらいのマイナスもなきゃ
because without a little bit of negativity,
って思うくらいにいい感じ
it feels just right!
まあねこんなに幸せでいいので
Well, it's fine to be this happy,
だって私自分で選んだんだから
because I chose this path myself!
犬は駆け回り 猫は可愛いし
Dogs run around, cats are cute,
青い鳥は飛ぶ みんながいる！
and blue birds fly—everyone's here!
本日はケの日普通にいい
Today's an ordinary day, perfectly fine,
一生で一番ヤングな日だけど
the most youthful day of my life,
仕方ないです って感じで冷めたりもしてるよ
but oh well, I'm kind of unfazed by it too!
サプライズのメッセージ
Surprise messages,
驚くはずないって大決まり
are no surprise at all, as expected!
一昨年の今は他人で
Two years ago today we were strangers,
これまではたくさんもっと
and until then, more and more—
無駄かもってこと恋愛とかしてたね
wasted time on things like romance and all.
今は本当にお大好きで！
But now I love you so, so much!
あなたこんなに幸せでいいのかな？
I wonder if it's okay for you to be this happy?
なんて本当そのこと心配ないけど
Though I'm not really worried about that,
だってちょっとくらいの試練とかもなきゃ
because without a little bit of hardship,
って思うくらいのいい感じ
it feels just right!
まあね結局幸せでいいので
Well, in the end it's fine to be happy,
だって私ちゃんと戦ったんだから
because I fought hard for this!
おみこしに乗って 花火も上げて いいことはぜんぶ 一度にしよう！
Riding the portable shrine, setting off fireworks, let's have all the good things at once!
私こんなに幸せでいいのかな？
I wonder if it's okay to be this happy?
なんて本当はそのこと悩んでないけど
Though I'm not really worrying about that,
だってちょっとくらいのマイナスもなきゃ
because without a little bit of negativity,
って思うくらいにいい感じ
it feels just right!
まあねこんなに幸せでいいので
Well, it's fine to be this happy,
だって私自分で選んだんだから
because I chose this path myself!
犬は駆け回り 猫は可愛いし
Dogs run around, cats are cute,
青い鳥は飛ぶ みんながいる最高に今に
and blue birds fly—everyone's here in this supreme moment!
おめでとうだよ！
Congratulations!
なんかをもっと作っちゃお
Let's make even more,
幸せでもいいじゃん！
happiness is totally fine!
Ayo ayo ayo
Ayo ayo ayo ayo ayo
Mic check mic check one two, mic check one two, ayo!
Ayo yoyo!
What's up?
DJ DJ Zeta on the house, yo!
So, next song is the rap of the night. Actually it's not even rap. I don't know if you guys—it's the rap of the night for sure.
Can you can you trust can you trust me enough if I say it's a rap song? What if it's like a ballad?
A ballad song?
Anyway, so, I have a really cool song and um I want you guys to scream with me!
Okay, scream with me. Okay?
Practice your screaming now.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, okay. Okay?
I want you guys to prepare your highest voice.
Let's go!
Let's go! I want you guys to scream as loud as you can, okay?
Because this is the last song!
Let's go! Let's end it with a bang!
思い出すのは君の歌 会話よりも鮮明だ
What I remember is your song, more vividly than conversation.
どこに行ってしまったの いつも探すんだよ
Where did you go? I'm always searching for it.
思い出すのは君の歌 歌い笑う顔が鮮明だ
What I remember is your song, your smiling face as you sang.
君に似合うんだよ ずっと見ていたいよ
It suits you so well, I want to watch you forever.
でも最後にみたいのは きっともう君の夢の中
But what I want to see at the end is surely inside your dreams.
もう一度また聞かせてくれないよ 聞きたいんだ
Let me hear it once more, please. I want to hear it.
もっと騒げ怪獣の歌
Make some more noise, monster's song!
まだ消えない 夢の歌 歌って 君がいつでも 歌う怪獣の歌
Still not fading, the song of our dreams. Sing it, the monster's song you always sing.
まだ消えない 口ずさんでしまうよ
Still not fading, I end up humming it.
落ちてく過去は鮮明で 見せたい未来は繊細で
The falling past is clear, the future I want to show is delicate.
過ぎてく日々には鈍感な君へ
To you, who are insensitive to the passing days—
もっと騒げ怪獣の歌 まだ消えない 夢の歌 歌って
Make more noise, monster's song! Still not fading, sing the song of dreams!
君がいつでも歌う怪獣の歌 まだ消えない 口ずさんでしまうよ
The monster's song you always sing, still not fading, I end up humming it.
もっと騒げ怪獣の歌 まだ消えない 夢の歌 歌って
Make more noise, monster's song! Still not fading, sing the song of dreams!
君がいつでも歌う怪獣の歌 まだ消えない 口ずさんでしまうよ
The monster's song you always sing, still not fading, I end up humming it.
落ちてく過去は鮮明で 見せたい未来は繊細で 過ぎてく日々には鈍感な君へ
The falling past is clear, the future I want to show is delicate, to you, insensitive to passing days.
もっと騒げ怪獣の歌 まだ消えない 夢の歌 歌って 君がいつでも歌う怪獣の歌
Make more noise, monster's song! Still not fading, sing the song of dreams, the monster's song you always sing.
まだ消えない 口ずさんでしまうよ 君がいつでも歌う怪獣の歌 まだ消えない 口ずさんでしまうよ
Still not fading, I end up humming it. The monster's song you always sing, still not fading, I end up humming it.
ねえ 僕ら 眠れない夜に手を伸ばして 眠れない夜をまた伸ばして
Hey, us, reaching our hands out on sleepless nights, stretching out the sleepless nights once more.
眠くないまだね そんな日々でいたいのにな 懲りずに
Still not sleepy yet, wanting to stay in such days without learning our lesson.
手を伸ばして また伸ばして 眠れない夜をまた伸ばして
Reaching out, reaching out once more, stretching out sleepless nights once more.
眠くないまだね 眠れない夜をまた伸ばして
Still not sleepy yet, stretching out sleepless nights once more.
手を伸ばして また伸ばして そんなようにも歌おう
Reaching out, reaching out once more, let's sing like that too.
Yay!
How was it? Did you guys enjoy the performance?
Fantastic side eye, English.
Fantastic side-eye, English.
I hope you guys liked it!
I enjoyed it as well!
I've always wanted to do a mini-live, so it's a dream come true that I get to do a mini live for you.
I've always wanted to do a mini-live, so it's a dream come true that I get to do a mini-live for you.
And uh I have Vazzle with me, I have you guys with me, although you guys aren't live-fullish in front of me, it's okay.
And uh, I have Vazzle with me, I have you guys with me, although you guys aren't physically in front of me, it's okay.
Ah, I had so much fun.
Thank you for staying with me for the past two years.
Um here's to hopefully many, many years in the future, you know?
Many, many more! Many, many more!
Aku press kalian sampai habis!
I'll squeeze you until you're completely drained!
Enggak, enggak, kalian...
No, no, you guys...
Jadi hari ini kita berhenti di sini.
So today we're stopping here.
Kira-kira kita tuh mau ngasih tuh...
I wonder what we're going to give...
But, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but, but...
Not before, not before I do something, which is...